export const QAdata={
  getData(){
  return [
    {
      "question": "What is a Database Management System (DBMS)? What is a Database Management System (DBMS)? What is a Database Management System (DBMS)?",
      "answer": "A DBMS is a software application that allows users to create, manage, and access a database. It provides a structured way to store, organize, and retrieve data efficiently.",
      "keywords": ["software", "is", "users", "VIP", "Relational Database Model", "ACID properties"],
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the different levels of data abstraction in a DBMS?",
      "answer": "There are three main levels:\n" +
          "\n" +
          "Physical Level: Deals with the physical storage of data, like how it's organized on disks. (Lowest level)\n" +
          "Logical Level: Defines the structure and relationships between data, independent of physical storage. (Middle level)\n" +
          "View Level: Provides a customized view of the database for specific users or applications. (Highest level)",
      "keywords": ["Database", "MongoDB", "Health", "VIP", "Relational Database Model", "ACID properties"],
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the benefits of using a DBMS?",
      "answer": "Data Integrity: Ensures data accuracy and consistency through constraints and rules.\n" +
          "Data Security: Provides access controls and user permissions to protect sensitive data.\n" +
          "Data Sharing and Accessibility: Allows multiple users to access and manipulate data efficiently.\n" +
          "Data Backup and Recovery: Offers mechanisms to recover data in case of system failures." +
      "Data Integrity: Ensures data accuracy and consistency through constraints and rules.\n" +
          "Data Security: Provides access controls and user permissions to protect sensitive data.\n" +
          "Data Sharing and Accessibility: Allows multiple users to access and manipulate data efficiently.\n" +
          "Data Backup and Recovery: Offers mechanisms to recover data in case of system failures.",
      "keywords": ["Data Integrity", "Data Security", "Data Sharing and Accessibility", "Data Backup and Recovery", "Relational Database Model", "ACID properties"],
    },
    {
      "question": " What is normalization in a database?",
      "answer": " Normalization is a process of organizing data in tables to minimize redundancy (duplicate data) and improve data integrity. There are different normal forms (1NF, 2NF, 3NF) with increasing levels of strictness.",
      "keywords": ["Database", "MongoDB", "Health", "VIP", "Relational Database Model", "ACID properties"],
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the difference between a primary key and a foreign key?",
      "answer": "Primary Key: A unique identifier for each record in a table, ensuring no duplicates. It cannot be null.\n" +
          "Foreign Key: A column in one table that references the primary key of another table, linking related data. It can be null but often references a valid primary key value.",
      "keywords": ["Database", "MongoDB", "Health", "VIP", "Relational Database Model", "ACID properties"],
    },
    {
      "answer": "Twitter said the hackers had targeted its employees \"with access to internal systems and tools\".",
      "question": "What did the FBI say about the hack?",
      "keywords": ["Database", "MongoDB", "Health", "VIP", "Relational Database Model", "ACID properties"],
      "type": "sentence"
    },
    {
      "answer": "The FBI has launched an investigation after hackers hijacked Twitter accounts of a number of high-profile US figures in an apparent Bitcoin scam.",
      "question": "What happened to the Twitter accounts of the three?",
      "keywords": ["Database", "MongoDB", "Health", "VIP", "Relational Database Model", "ACID properties"],
      "type": "sentence"
    },
    {
      "answer": "One cyber-security expert said that the breach could have been a lot worse in other circumstances.",
      "question": "What did the FBI say was the worst case scenario?",
      "keywords": ["Database", "MongoDB", "Health", "VIP", "Relational Database Model", "ACID properties"],
      "type": "sentence"
    },
    {
      "answer": "\"We know they [the hackers] used this access to take control of many highly-visible (including verified) ac counts and Tweet on their behalf,\" the company said in a series of tweets.",
      "question": "What did the FBI say about the hack?",
      "keywords": ["Database", "MongoDB", "Health", "VIP", "Relational Database Model", "ACID properties"],
      "type": "sentence"
    },
    {
      "answer": "\" You send $1,000, I send you back $2,000.",
      "question": "How much did the FBI send back?",
      "keywords": ["Database", "MongoDB", "Health", "VIP", "Relational Database Model", "ACID properties"],
      "type": "sentence"
    },
    {
      "answer": "President Trump's account was not compromised, the White House said.",
      "question": "What did the president say about the hack?",
      "keywords": ["Database", "MongoDB", "Health", "VIP", "Relational Database Model", "ACID properties"],
      "type": "sentence"
    },
    {
      "answer": "It added that \"significant steps\" had been taken to limit access to such internal systems and tools while th e company's investigation continues.",
      "question": "What did the FBI say about the hack?",
      "keywords": ["Database", "MongoDB", "Health", "VIP", "Relational Database Model", "ACID properties"],
      "type": "sentence"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Republican Senator Josh Hawley has written to the company asking if President Trump's account had been vulnerable.",
      "question": "What is the name of the person who wrote to Twitter?",
      "keywords": ["Database", "MongoDB", "Health", "VIP", "Relational Database Model", "ACID properties"],
      "type": "sentence"
    },
    {
      "answer": "\"I'm feeling generous because of Covid-19,\" the tweet added, along with a Bitcoin link address.",
      "question": "What did the tweet say?",
      "keywords": ["Database", "MongoDB", "Health", "VIP", "Relational Database Model", "ACID properties"],
      "type": "sentence"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Cryptoforhealth is also a registered user name on Instagram, apparently set up contemporaneously to the hack.",
      "question": "What is the name of the hacker?",
      "keywords": ["Database", "MongoDB", "Health", "VIP", "Relational Database Model", "ACID properties"],
      "type": "sentence"
    },
    {
      "answer": "The Instagram profile also posted a message that said: \"It was a charity attack.",
      "question": "What was the message?",
      "keywords": ["Database", "MongoDB", "Health", "VIP", "Relational Database Model", "ACID properties"],
      "type": "sentence"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Dmitri Alperovitch, who co-founded cyber-security company CrowdStrike, told Reuters news agency: \"Thi s appears to be the worst hack of a major social media platform yet.",
      "question": "Who co-founded CrowdStrike?",
      "keywords": ["Database", "MongoDB", "Health", "VIP", "Relational Database Model", "ACID properties"],
      "type": "sentence"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Cameron Winklevoss, who was declared the world's first Bitcoin billionaire in 2017 along with his twin brot her Tyler, tweeted a message on Wednesday warning people not to participate in the \"scam\".",
      "question": "Who was the first Bitcoin billionaire?",
      "keywords": ["Database", "MongoDB", "Health", "VIP", "Relational Database Model", "ACID properties"],
      "type": "sentence"
    },
    {
      "answer": "But as the first such tweet from Mr Musk's account was removed, another one appeared, then a third.",
      "question": "What was the first tweet from Mr Musk's account removed?",
      "keywords": ["Database", "MongoDB", "Health", "VIP", "Relational Database Model", "ACID properties"],
      "type": "sentence"
    },
    {
      "answer": "The name \"Anthony Elias\" was used to register the website, but may be a pseudonym - it appears to be a play on \"an alias\".",
      "question": "What is the name of the website?",
      "keywords": ["Database", "MongoDB", "Health", "VIP", "Relational Database Model", "ACID properties"],
      "type": "sentence"
    },
    {
      "answer": "\"Twitter actually has a good history of being forward-thinking and proactive in this space.",
      "question": "what is the twitter history?",
      "keywords": ["Database", "MongoDB", "Health", "VIP", "Relational Database Model", "ACID properties"],
      "type": "sentence"
    },
    {
      "answer": "But whatever th e source of this attack [it seems they have] still not done enough.",
      "question": "what is the twitter attack?",
      "keywords": ["Database", "MongoDB", "Health", "VIP", "Relational Database Model", "ACID properties"],
      "type": "sentence"
    },
  ]
},
}